<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-05-25T17:11:18-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Scott Fowler</title><subtitle>Acrylic and Watercolor Artist</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Cold, Cold River</title><link href="/creative/writing/2023/05/25/cw-cold-river/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cold, Cold River" /><published>2023-05-25T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-05-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/creative/writing/2023/05/25/cw-cold-river</id><content type="html" xml:base="/creative/writing/2023/05/25/cw-cold-river/"><![CDATA[<figure class="alignleft">
    <img src="https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:720/0*tnSTH85cD6dp3wyl" alt="photo of a cabin in the woods at dusk" />
    <figcaption class="text-center">Photo by <a class="af ns" href="https://unsplash.com/@derek_pdx?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=referral" rel="noopener ugc nofollow" target="_blank">Derek Sears</a> on <a class="af ns" href="https://unsplash.com?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=referral" rel="noopener ugc nofollow" target="_blank">Unsplash</a></figcaption>
</figure>

<h4 id="i-do-a-bit-of-creative-writing-from-time-to-time-heres-my-latest-attempt-this-is-called-cold-cold-river">I do a bit of creative writing from time to time. Here’s my latest attempt. This is called <em>Cold, Cold River</em>!</h4>

<p>The man sat in the front porch rocker fidgeting, waiting for the woman to drown. The chair protested with loud, agonizing creaks as it listed back and forth. His boots marked time on the wooden floor like a metronome. Time seemed to stand still.
<!--more--></p>

<p>The urgent orchestra of cicadas eclipsed the woman’s frantic splashing. They shouted their late summer evening concerto for the whole world to hear. The ebb and flow of their resonance reminded him of movies like War of the Worlds. Sinister alien armies coming to infest Earth by draining the masses to a bloody pulp. No matter — out here at the cabin on the lake — no one would hear her struggle.</p>

<p>“Hurry up and die,” he said at last.</p>

<p>He scratched at his day-old stubble, a jagged fingernail snagging beard. With listless eyes, he trimmed its remains with uneven, yellowed teeth. And spat the residue into the distance. It disappeared like it never existed.</p>

<p>It was a simple fact. He would be here until this whole thing was over, waiting for the priest. The priest was on his way. The priest would tell him what to do next.</p>

<p>Straightening his leg, he reached deep into his front pocket and pulled out his pocket knife. He scrutinized the knife, turning it over in his hands, and finally unfolded the blade. For a moment, he held the knife in his left hand and considered the bad trimming job he’d executed with his teeth. He moved the blade in short strokes over the coarse end of the nail to smooth it.</p>

<p>After blowing away the residue, he examined his work. He said, “Not bad, not bad at all.”</p>

<p>The sun slipped behind the distant mountain, hidden from the world for another day. As the song of the locust heightened, he leaned back in the chair and closed his eyes. Sleep came immediately.</p>

<p>When the splashing stopped, he never heard it.</p>]]></content><author><name>Scott Fowler</name></author><category term="Creative" /><category term="Writing" /><category term="scene" /><category term="mystery" /><category term="thriller" /><category term="suspense" /><category term="writing" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Derek Sears on Unsplash I do a bit of creative writing from time to time. Here’s my latest attempt. This is called Cold, Cold River! The man sat in the front porch rocker fidgeting, waiting for the woman to drown. The chair protested with loud, agonizing creaks as it listed back and forth. His boots marked time on the wooden floor like a metronome. Time seemed to stand still.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">IxDF NWA June 2023 Meet-up</title><link href="/ixdf/2023/05/21/ixdf-june-meetup/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IxDF NWA June 2023 Meet-up" /><published>2023-05-21T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-05-21T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/ixdf/2023/05/21/ixdf-june-meetup</id><content type="html" xml:base="/ixdf/2023/05/21/ixdf-june-meetup/"><![CDATA[<figure class="alignleft">
    <img src="/assets/images/posts/ixdf-june-shire-01.jpg" alt="The Shire Gastropub in Downtown Rogers" />
</figure>

<h3 id="thursday-june-8--the-shire--6-8-pm">Thursday, June 8 | The Shire | 6-8 pm</h3>

<p>Hi IxDF NW Arkansas, let’s meet up at <a href="https://www.theshirenwa.com/">The Shire Gastropub</a>, share UX design insights and resources, discuss UX problems you are facing now, or just chat.</p>

<p>Maybe do a little bit of karaoke this time? Maybe I’ll do some Barry Manilow for everyone. “Her name was Lola, she was a showgirl.” LOL.</p>

<dl>
  <dt>Time &amp; Location</dt>
  <dd>June 8, 6-8 pm
The Shire Gastropub in downtown Rogers, AR</dd>
  <dt>Get FREE Tickets</dt>
  <dd><a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/ixdf-nw-arkansas-june-2023-meet-up-tickets-640146614757" class="btn btn-primary btn-lg">Eventbrite</a></dd>
</dl>]]></content><author><name>Scott Fowler</name></author><category term="IxDF" /><category term="UXDesign" /><category term="Networking" /><category term="NWArkansas" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thursday, June 8 | The Shire | 6-8 pm Hi IxDF NW Arkansas, let’s meet up at The Shire Gastropub, share UX design insights and resources, discuss UX problems you are facing now, or just chat. Maybe do a little bit of karaoke this time? Maybe I’ll do some Barry Manilow for everyone. “Her name was Lola, she was a showgirl.” LOL. Time &amp; Location June 8, 6-8 pm The Shire Gastropub in downtown Rogers, AR Get FREE Tickets Eventbrite]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">IxDF NWA May 2023 Roundup</title><link href="/ixdf/2023/05/12/ixdf-may-roundup/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IxDF NWA May 2023 Roundup" /><published>2023-05-12T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-05-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/ixdf/2023/05/12/ixdf-may-roundup</id><content type="html" xml:base="/ixdf/2023/05/12/ixdf-may-roundup/"><![CDATA[<figure class="alignleft">
    <img src="/assets/images/posts/ixdf-may-aloft-01.jpg" alt="IxDF NWA members gather at Aloft Lounge in Rogers" />
</figure>

<h3 id="sharing-ux-journeys">Sharing UX Journeys</h3>

<p>Mark Francis and I arrived at the <strong><a href="https://www.marriott.com/en-us/hotels/rogal-aloft-rogers-bentonville/overview/">Aloft Lounge and Bar</a> </strong> before anyone else in the group and discovered that their oven had went kaput at the very last minute.</p>

<p>Broken. Out of order. Out of commission.</p>

<p>We were looking forward to having a bit food; personally, I was in need of fish and chips, but alas, we were denied. Not to be totally done in, we ordered a beer instead and settled in for the meet up. 
<!--more--></p>

<figure class="alignleft">
    <img src="/assets/images/posts/ixdf-may-aloft-02.jpg" alt="Mark talking with Jericho" />
      <figcaption>Mark talks with Jericho.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>But even with the oven out of commission, Aloft Lounge and Bar did not disappoint. A large public area complete with ample couches, chairs and tables, full bar, snack bar and billiard table, there was more than enough room for all of us to spread out, be comfortable, and get to know one another better. The service was stellar.</p>

<p>After hanging out, ordering drinks (plus some much-needed Door Dash) and building relationships for an hour or so, several people shared their individual UX journeys and inspired the group. Those that shared included Jennifer Hart, Jenifer Paredes, Tracy Lindstrom, Alexandra Hinds, and Ryan Phillips.</p>
<figure class="alignright">
    <img src="/assets/images/posts/ixdf-may-aloft-03.jpg" alt="a smart selfie of Scott and Shauna" />
      <figcaption>A smart selfie of Scott and Shauna.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>One of the best aspects of our group is the wide range of diversity in practical knowledge that we share with each other. Our members are from all over NW Arkansas and our varied backgrounds range from graphic design and prepress work to seasoned UX Designers and user researchers.</p>

<p>If this sounds like fun or you’d like to learn more about the UX field, come out to our next monthly meeting and bring a friend. I’ll be posting the details of our June meeting very soon.</p>]]></content><author><name>Scott Fowler</name></author><category term="IxDF" /><category term="UXDesign" /><category term="Networking" /><category term="NWArkansas" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing UX Journeys Mark Francis and I arrived at the Aloft Lounge and Bar before anyone else in the group and discovered that their oven had went kaput at the very last minute. Broken. Out of order. Out of commission. We were looking forward to having a bit food; personally, I was in need of fish and chips, but alas, we were denied. Not to be totally done in, we ordered a beer instead and settled in for the meet up.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Spectra May 2023 Meet-up</title><link href="/spectra/2023/04/27/spectra-may-meetup/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Spectra May 2023 Meet-up" /><published>2023-04-27T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-04-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/spectra/2023/04/27/spectra-may-meetup</id><content type="html" xml:base="/spectra/2023/04/27/spectra-may-meetup/"><![CDATA[<figure class="alignleft">
    <img src="/assets/images/posts/spectra-may1.jpg" alt="artists painting in a group" />
</figure>

<h3 id="fellowship-nwa-art-ministry">Fellowship NWA Art Ministry</h3>

<p><a href="https://www.fellowshipnwa.org/spectra/" target="_blank">Spectra NW Arkansas</a> is hosting a meeting at the Fellowship Rogers Chapel on May 1, 2023 at 6pm to show artwork created while meditating on the book of 1 Peter. We get together to present our artwork to encourage and inspire each other.</p>

<p>Spectra NW Arkansas is a community of adult NWA Christian Artists-photographers, painters, graphic designers, and writers of prose and poetry—all with the same goals. If you’d like to come out and see what we’ve created.<a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/Fellowship+Bible+Church+of+Northwest+Arkansas/@36.2844273,-94.1358969,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m6!3m5!1s0x87c916a168d075dd:0x416c05ccaebfeb33!8m2!3d36.284423!4d-94.133322!16s%2Fg%2F1tjxg5pq">Visit SPECTRA NWA</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>Scott Fowler</name></author><category term="SPECTRA" /><category term="ArtMinistry" /><category term="NWArkansas" /><category term="FellowshipBibleChurch" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fellowship NWA Art Ministry Spectra NW Arkansas is hosting a meeting at the Fellowship Rogers Chapel on May 1, 2023 at 6pm to show artwork created while meditating on the book of 1 Peter. We get together to present our artwork to encourage and inspire each other. Spectra NW Arkansas is a community of adult NWA Christian Artists-photographers, painters, graphic designers, and writers of prose and poetry—all with the same goals. If you’d like to come out and see what we’ve created.Visit SPECTRA NWA.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">IxDF May 2023 Meet-up</title><link href="/ixdf/2023/04/19/ixdf-may-meetup/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IxDF May 2023 Meet-up" /><published>2023-04-19T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-04-19T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/ixdf/2023/04/19/ixdf-may-meetup</id><content type="html" xml:base="/ixdf/2023/04/19/ixdf-may-meetup/"><![CDATA[<figure class="alignleft">
    <img src="/assets/images/posts/ixdf-may-aloft.jpg" alt="Aloft in Rogers" />
</figure>

<p>Well, well. We had such a great time at the April meeting, it’s already time to announce the May one. Time flies when you’re having fun, right?</p>

<p>This May we’ll partake in some good food and drink, play a bit of billiards and share some of our individual UX career journeys with each other. Come out, join us, and make some new friends. You don’t have to join IxDF to be a part of the group and everyone and their plus ones are always invited.</p>

<dl>
  <dt>Location</dt>
  <dd>Aloft Rogers</dd>
  <dt>Address</dt>
  <dd>1103 S 52nd St, Rogers, Arkansas, US, 72758</dd>
  <dt>Date/Time</dt>
  <dd>May 11, 2023/6-8pm</dd>
  <dt>Get FREE Tickets</dt>
  <dd><a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/ixdf-nw-arkansas-may-2023-meet-up-tickets-620918904157">Sign up at Eventbrite</a></dd>
</dl>]]></content><author><name>Scott Fowler</name></author><category term="IxDF" /><category term="UXDesign" /><category term="Networking" /><category term="NWArkansas" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, well. We had such a great time at the April meeting, it’s already time to announce the May one. Time flies when you’re having fun, right? This May we’ll partake in some good food and drink, play a bit of billiards and share some of our individual UX career journeys with each other. Come out, join us, and make some new friends. You don’t have to join IxDF to be a part of the group and everyone and their plus ones are always invited. Location Aloft Rogers Address 1103 S 52nd St, Rogers, Arkansas, US, 72758 Date/Time May 11, 2023/6-8pm Get FREE Tickets Sign up at Eventbrite]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">IxDF NWA April 2023 Round-up</title><link href="/ixdf/2023/04/17/ixdf-meetup/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IxDF NWA April 2023 Round-up" /><published>2023-04-17T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/ixdf/2023/04/17/ixdf-meetup</id><content type="html" xml:base="/ixdf/2023/04/17/ixdf-meetup/"><![CDATA[<figure class="alignleft">
    <img src="/assets/images/posts/ixdf-april1.jpg" alt="IxDF Members at April 2023" />
</figure>

<h3 id="food-friends-and-karaoke">Food, Friends and Karaoke</h3>

<p>Oh, my goodness UX peeps! What an incredible time we had at the April Meet-up! The Interaction Design Foundation (IxDF) of NW Arkansas had their monthly meeting last night and took over The Shire in downtown Rogers. We had over 20 folks from NW Arkansas area show up. J.B. Hunt showed up to represent. Fellow J.B. Hunt UXers Shauna Mauk, Pauletta Starkenberg, Rachel May, Jen Hart, and Eduardo Martinez were there along with a large contingent of Wal-Mart and Tyson folks.
<!--more--></p>

<p>The best thing about all this is how we’re building honest relationships with our peers throughout NW Arkansas. I found that I have a lot in common with the people I met. I was able to relate with friends about some of my past experiences in newspapers, embroidery, and what I’m learning now.</p>

<figure class="alignleft">
    <img src="/assets/images/posts/ixdf-april2.jpg" alt="IxDF Members at April 2023 Meet-up" />
</figure>

<p>If you haven’t been to one of our meet-ups, I have to say that you’re truly missing a great opportunity to expand your UX network. Our group is growing by leaps and bounds. We’re anticipating 40 people in May. I’ll be sending out May’s invite within the next week on</p>
<ul>
  <li><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/">LinkedIn</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/">Eventbrite</a></li>
  <li><a href="https://www.interaction-design.org/local-group/north-america/united-states/arkansas/nw-arkansas">IxDF NW Arkansas</a></li>
</ul>

<p>Please come out and join us. You don’t have to join IxDF to be a part of the group and everyone and their plus ones are always invited.</p>]]></content><author><name>Scott Fowler</name></author><category term="IxDF" /><category term="UXDesign" /><category term="Networking" /><category term="NWArkansas" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Food, Friends and Karaoke Oh, my goodness UX peeps! What an incredible time we had at the April Meet-up! The Interaction Design Foundation (IxDF) of NW Arkansas had their monthly meeting last night and took over The Shire in downtown Rogers. We had over 20 folks from NW Arkansas area show up. J.B. Hunt showed up to represent. Fellow J.B. Hunt UXers Shauna Mauk, Pauletta Starkenberg, Rachel May, Jen Hart, and Eduardo Martinez were there along with a large contingent of Wal-Mart and Tyson folks.]]></summary></entry></feed>